<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>wonslung Fire Stick help</title>
    <link>https://wonslung.github.io/firestickhelp/</link>
    <description>Recent content on wonslung Fire Stick help</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Released under the MIT license</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Jul 2017 01:23:23 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://wonslung.github.io/firestickhelp/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>wonslung Fire Sticks</title>
      <link>https://wonslung.github.io/firestickhelp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jul 2017 01:23:23 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wonslung.github.io/firestickhelp/</guid>
      <description> Thanks for buying a wonslung Fire Stick Table of Contents:  Getting Started  What&amp;rsquo;s in the Box Connecting the Fire Stick The Remote Connecting to wifi  Navigating FireOS
 Kodi
 Frequently Asked Questions
 Trouble Shooting
by wonslung  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started</title>
      <link>https://wonslung.github.io/firestickhelp/getting-started/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2017 23:32:40 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wonslung.github.io/firestickhelp/getting-started/</guid>
      <description>What&amp;rsquo;s in the box  Amazon documentation USB power cable Fire Tv Alexa remote Amazon Fire Stick HDMI adapter dongle USB power adapter  Connecting the Fire Stick Hint
you can use a powered usb port instead of the wall adapter if your television has one
 The Remote Using the remote is pretty simple.
 Use the navigation buttons to move through menus. Use the select button to select highlighted menu item.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Navigating Fire Os</title>
      <link>https://wonslung.github.io/firestickhelp/fireos/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2017 04:54:42 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wonslung.github.io/firestickhelp/fireos/</guid>
      <description>Navigating Menus Use the navigation button on the remote to move through the menus. You can always return to the &amp;ldquo;Home&amp;rdquo; Menu by pushing the &amp;#x2302; (Home) button on the remote

Most users want to get into Kodi Immediately. This is done by navigating down to &amp;ldquo;My Apps and Games&amp;rdquo; from the &amp;ldquo;Home&amp;rdquo; menu and selecting the Kodi App. Menu Options Attention
Unless you have Amazon Prime&amp;trade; The &amp;ldquo;Your Videos, Movies, and TV Shows&amp;rdquo; will cost money.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kodi</title>
      <link>https://wonslung.github.io/firestickhelp/kodi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jul 2017 04:52:25 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wonslung.github.io/firestickhelp/kodi/</guid>
      <description>What is Kodi? Kodi is software designed to serve as a media center. With 3rd party addons, it can play almost any type of video file and stream media from all over the internet. (3rd party addons are not affliated or supported by the kodi development team)
First Start
When you first start Kodi please allow 60-90 seconds before attempting use.
 How to navigate Kodi Note
These instructions are specific to the wonslung FireStick Skin kodi build</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Frequently Asked Questions</title>
      <link>https://wonslung.github.io/firestickhelp/faqs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2017 01:44:46 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wonslung.github.io/firestickhelp/faqs/</guid>
      <description>How do i register my Fire Stick to my Amazon account?  Make sure you have setup wifi Navigate to Settings Navigate to My Account and press the select button on your remote Press the select button on your remote to confirm Enter in your Amazon account information  Do I need an Amazon Account to use a wonslung Fire Stick? I set up each wonslung Fire Stick with a placeholder amazon account.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trouble Shooting</title>
      <link>https://wonslung.github.io/firestickhelp/trouble-shooting/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2017 01:44:19 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wonslung.github.io/firestickhelp/trouble-shooting/</guid>
      <description> foo bar </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>License</title>
      <link>https://wonslung.github.io/firestickhelp/license/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2016 20:10:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wonslung.github.io/firestickhelp/license/</guid>
      <description>Copyright &amp;copy; 2017 wonslung wonslung@gmail.com
Copyright &amp;copy; 2016 Digitalcraftsman digitalcraftsman@protonmail.com
Copyright &amp;copy; 2016 Martin Donath martin.donath@squidfunk.com
Permission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person obtaining a copy of this software and associated documentation files (the &amp;ldquo;Software&amp;rdquo;), to deal in the Software without restriction, including without limitation the rights to use, copy, modify, merge, publish, distribute, sublicense, and/or sell copies of the Software, and to permit persons to whom the Software is furnished to do so, subject to the following conditions:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>